OLEG TABACHNIKOW

Frontend Engineer

Tel Aviv - Jaffa, Israel · +972539240665

olegtabachnikow@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/olegtabachnikow

As a highly motivated frontend developer, my experience covers Israel and United States. I have extensive experience building single page applications and mobile applications with a variety of programming languages. I constantly seek to improve my developer skill set by completing additional courses and staying up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies. In fact, I was even requested to return and teach certain courses due to my proficiency and soft skills.

SKILLS

- Frontend: React, Redux, NextJS, Typescript, Javascript, React Native, Ant Design, i18n, Framer Motion, HTML5, CSS3
- Backend: NodeJS, Express, MongoDB
- Tools: Postman, Github, Firebase, Figma, Adobe
- Experience with NoSQL, JSON and REST APIs

Languages:

- English Full Professional Proficiency
- Hebrew Basic
- Russian Native

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2023 – CURRENT TIME FRONTEND ENGINEER, SRISA, ITALY

- Integrated authentication and authorization functionalities using NextAuth.js to facilitate secure user authentication, including login and registration.
- Configured NextAuth.js to support various authentication providers, such as email/password, social logins (Google, Facebook, GitHub, etc.), ensuring a flexible and user-friendly authentication process.
- Leveraged Next.js, a React framework, for server-side rendering and efficient client-side routing, providing a performant and SEO-friendly web application.
- Implemented Redux Thunk middleware to manage asynchronous actions, state management, and data flow within the Next.js application, enabling smooth user interactions and data handling.

JANUARY 2023 – JUNE 2023

FRONTEND ENGINEER, EDEAL INC, USA

- Conceptualized and developed a comprehensive, reusable component library, streamlining the development process and promoting consistent design across projects.
- Developed a two fully functional websites using HTML, CSS, and React to showcase company products/services and enhance online presence.
- Implemented SEO best practices to optimize website and landing page for search engines, resulting in increased organic traffic and improved search rankings.
- Integrated analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) to track website performance, user behavior, and conversion rates, providing valuable insights for data-driven decision-making.

NOVEMBER 2022 – MARCH 2023 FRONTEND ENGINEER, GET ROBO VPN, RUSSIA

• Developed a responsive and user-friendly Single Page Application (SPA) for seamless integration into the Telegram Web App Bot.

MARCH 2022 – AUGUST 2022 FRONTEND ENGINEER, AVA MIND, ISRAEL

 Assumed a leadership role in strategizing project roadmap, effectively coordinating with key stakeholders to maintain alignment throughout the development process.

EDUCATION

2022

YANDEX PRACTICUM, ISRAEL

2017

ECONOMICS & ENTERPRISE MANAGEMENT, POLOTSK STATE UNIVERSITY